A Guide to the Records of T. Marshall Hahn Jr, 1962-1974
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series II, 1965-1967
  - O-miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 680)
  - Organizations, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 681)
  - P-miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 682)
  - Personnel- Richmond: Mr. J.W. Garber, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 683)
  - Personnel- Blacksburg: Mr. E.B. Evans, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 684)
  - Philosophy and Religion: Dr. Norman L. Groner, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 685)
  - Physics: Dr. J.A. Jacobs, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 686)
  - Physical Education: Dr. W.E. McCubbin, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 687)
  - Placement: Dr. W.H. Cato, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 688)
  - Planning Engineer: Mr. H.P.C. Vandenburg, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 689)
  - Plant Pathology and Physiology: Dr. H.B. Couch, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 690)
  - Poultry Science: Dr. C.E. Howes, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 691)
  - Presidents Council, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 692)
  - Purchasing Agent: Mr. H.W. Swink, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 693)
  - Public Relations #1, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 694)
  - Public Relations #2, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 695)
  - Public Relations #3, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 696)
  - Q-miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 697)
  - R-miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 698)
  - Recommendations, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 699)
  - Registrar- R.E. Keller, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 700)
  - Regional Education Laboratory #1, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 701)
  - Regional Education Laboratory #2, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 702)
  - Research Division: Dr. W.B. Harrison, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 703)
  - Reston #1, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 703a)
  - Reston #2, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 704)
  - Reston #3, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 705)
  - Reston #4, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 706)
  - Retirement- Faculty, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 707)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 708)
  - Salaries, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 709)
  - Mr. Lon K. Savage, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 710)
  - Scholarships and Grants #1, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 711)
  - Scholarships and Grants #2, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 712)
  - Scholarships and Grants #3, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 713)
  - Scholarships- Harry F. Byrd, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 714)
  - Smithfield, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 715)
  - Social and Cultural Committee, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 716)
  - Speaking Engagements Correspondence, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 717)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 718)
  - State Council of Higher Education: Dr. P.B. Woodard #1, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 719)
  - State Council of Higher Education: Dr. P.B. Woodard #2, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 720)
  - State Board of Education, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 721)
  - State Technical Services, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 722)
  - Statistics: Dr. Boyd Harshbarger, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 723)
  - Status of Women, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 724)
  - Student Affairs: Dr. James W. Dean, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 725)
  - Student Affairs: Mr. A.C. Payne, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 726)
  - Student Affairs: Dean Audrey Rentz, Dean of Women, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 727)
  - Student Affairs: Dean J. Gordon Brown, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 728)
  - Student Letters: To and From, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 729)
  - Student Letters: Others- Parents and Friends #1, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 730)
  - Student Letters: Others- Parents and Friends #2, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 731)
  - Student Activities Committee, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 732)
  - Student Organizations #1, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 733)
  - Student Organizations #2, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 734)
  - Summer Orientation, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 734a)
  - Summer Orientation Committee, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 735)
  - Surveys ans Questionnaires, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 736)
  - T-miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 737)
  - Technical Education, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 738)
  - Tech Festival, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 739)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 740)
  - Treasurer, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 741)
  - U-miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 742)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 743)
  - University Research Park, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 744)
  - Virginia Agricultural Conference Board, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 745)
  - V.A.R.C.: Dr. William H. McFarlane, Director #1, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 746)
  - V.A.R.C.: Dr. William H. McFarlane, Director #2, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 747)
  - Virginia Tech Athletic Association: Mr. F.o. Moseley, Director, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 748)
  - VALC, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 749)
  - Vice President: Dr. Warren W. Brandt, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 750)
  - V-miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 751)
  - University Academic Council, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 752)
  - Virginia Department of Agriculture, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 753)
  - Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 754)
  - VPI Educational Foundation, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 755)
  - Veterinary Science, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 756)
  - Virginia Code Commission, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 757)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 758)
  - Virginia Truck Experiment Station: Dr. W.H. Brittingham, Director, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 759)
  - Visiting Scholar Program, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 760)
  - W-miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 761)
  - Water Pollution, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 762)
  - Water Resources, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 763)
  - Will-Lane Dinner, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 764)
  - YMCA, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 765)
  - A-miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 766)
  - Accrediting- National Commission on Accrediting- E.C.P.D., 1967 (Box 22, Folder 767)
  - Accountant: Mr. Carl E. Burke, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 768)
  - Admissions and Records: Dr. M.P. Lacy, Dean #1, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 769)
  - Admissions and Records: Dr. M.P. Lacy, Dean #2, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 770)
  - Aerospace Engineering: Dr. J.B. Eades, Department Head, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 771)
  - Agricultural College: Dr. Wilson B. Bell, Dean, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 772)
  - Agricultural Economics: Dr. James E. Martin, Department Head, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 773)
  - Agricultural Engineering: Professor E.T. Swink, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 774)
  - Airport, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 775)
  - Agriculture- Resident Instruction: Dr. T.J. Horn, Director, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 776)
  - Agronomy, Dr. H.L. Dunton, Department Head, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 777)
  - Aircraft, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 778)
  - Air University, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 779)
  - Alumni Alphabetical #1, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 780)
  - Alumni Alphabetical #2, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 781)
  - Alumni Alphabetical #3, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 782)
  - Alumni- President, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 783)
  - Alumni Contributions Alphabetical, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 784)
  - Alumni Association General #1, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 785)
  - Alumni Association General #2, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 786)
  - Alumni: Dr. J.W. Dean, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 787)
  - American Association of Engineering Education, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 788)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 789)
  - American Association for Higher Education, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 790)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 791)
  - American Association of University Women, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 792)
  - American Council on Education, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 793)
  - Anaerobic Laboratory- Proposal, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 794)
  - Animal Science: Professor G.W. Litton, Department Head, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 795)
  - Applications- Positions, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 796)
  - College of Arts and Science: Dean Leslie F. Malpass, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 797)
  - Association of Land-Grant Colleges and Universities- National #1, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 798)
  - Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities (National), 1967 (Box 22, Folder 799)
  - Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities (Southern), 1967 (Box 22, Folder 800)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 801)
  - Association of State Colleges and Universities, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 802)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 803)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 804)
  - Attorney General of Virginia, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 805)
  - Atlantic Council Minutes, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 806)
  - Architecture, College of, Dean Charles Burchard, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 807)
  - B-miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 808)
  - Bailey Research Trust, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 809)
  - Basketball, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 810)
  - Biochemistry Nutrition: Dr. Kendall W. King, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 811)
  - Biographies, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 812)
  - Biology, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 813)
  - Blacksburg, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 814)
  - Budget Director, Mr. L.M. Kuhn, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 815)
  - Budget Matters #1, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 816)
  - Budget #2, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 817)
  - Budget Matters #3, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 818)
  - Buildings and Grounds: Mr. Wm. Sterrett, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 819)
  - Business, College of: Dean H.H. Mitchell, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 820)
  - Business Manager: Mr. E.B. Evans, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 821)
  - C-miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 822)
  - Centennial, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 823)
  - Center for Vocational and Technical Education, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 824)
  - Chemical Engineering: Dr. G.H. Beyer, Head, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 825)
  - Chemistry: Dr. Allan F. Clifford, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 826)
  - Civil Rights, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 827)
  - Department of Civil Engineering, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 828)
  - College Calendar, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 829)
  - Commandant of Cadets, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 830)
  - Commencement Exercises, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 831)
  - Commission on Education for the Engineering Profession, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 832)
  - Committees: Building, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 833)
  - Committees: Catalog, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 834)
  - Committees: Commencement, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 835)
  - Committees: Computer, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 836)
  - Committees: VPI Facilities, Inc., 1967 (Box 23, Folder 837)
  - Committees: Faculty, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 838)
  - Committees: Graduate, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 839)
  - Committees: Judicial, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 840)
  - Committees: Library, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 841)
  - Committees: Social and Cultural, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 842)
  - Committees: Student Activities, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 843)
  - Committees: Traffic, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 844)
  - Committees: Women's Interdormitory Council, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 845)
  - Committees: University Council, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 846)
  - Committees: Resolutions, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 847)
  - Committees: Student Budget Board, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 848)
  - Committees, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 849)
  - Committees: Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 850)
  - Community Colleges: Dr. Dana Hamel, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 851)
  - Community Concerts, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 852)
  - Computing Center- University, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 853)
  - Conferences, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 854)
  - Consulting, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 856)
  - Continuing Education Center, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 857)
- Series III, 1967-1969
  - Council of Presidents, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 858)
  - Counseling Center: Dr. Thomas E. Cook, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 859)
  - D-Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 860)
  - Dairy Science: Dr. J.R. Nichols, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 861)
  - Dean- General, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 862)
  - Defense, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 863)
  - Development, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 864)
  - Development Council, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 865)
  - Dining Hall: Mr. H.P. King, Director, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 866)
  - Donner Foundation, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 867)
  - Economics: Dr. W.E. Schmidt, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 868)
  - Education: Dr. Rufus W. Beamer, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 869)
  - EDUCOM, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 870)
  - Electrical Engineering: Dr. W.A. Blackwell, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 871)
  - Engineering and Building: Governor's Office, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 872)
  - Engineering, College of: Dr. Willis G. Worchester, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 873)
  - Engineering Mechanics: Professor Dan H. Pletta, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 874)
  - English: Dr. Wilson Snipes, Head, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 875)
  - Enrollment Statistics, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 876)
  - Entomology Department: Dr. J.M. Grayson, Head, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 877)
  - Executive Bulletin, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 878)
  - Extension General, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 879)
  - Extension: Continuing Education Center- Dr. Roger L. Smith, Director, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 880)
  - Extension: 4-H Department, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 881)
  - Extension: State Technical Services- Dr. Robert L. Smith, Director, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 882)
  - Extension Division: Dr. W.E. Skelton, Dean, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 883)
  - F-Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 884)
  - Faculty Lists, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 885)
  - Faculty Senate, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 886)
  - Ferrum Junior College, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 887)
  - First National Exchange Bank of Virginia, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 888)
  - Forestry and Wildlife: Dr. J.F. Hosner, Head, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 889)
  - G-miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 890)
  - Gallagher Presidents' Report, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 891)
  - Geological Sciences: Dr. B.N. Cooper, Head, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 892)
  - Glee Club: Mr. Stanley Kingma, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 893)
  - Governor of Virginia: The Honorable Mills E. Godwin, Jr., 1967 (Box 24, Folder 894)
  - Governor's Day, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 895)
  - Dr. T. Marshall Hahn: Personal #1, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 896)
  - Dr. T. Marshall Hahn: Personal #2, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 897)
  - H-miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 898)
  - Graduate School: Dean F.W. Bull, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 899)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 900)
  - Higher Education Study Commission, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 901)
  - History, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 902)
  - Homecoming, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 903)
  - Home Economics, College of: Dean Laura J. Harper, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 904)
  - Hospital, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 905)
  - Honor Court, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 906)
  - Horticulture Department, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 907)
  - Housing: Off Campus- Mr. H.H. Peterson, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 908)
  - Informational Services: Mr. W.H. Strother, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 909)
  - Industrial Development, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 910)
  - I-miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 911)
  - Infirmary: Dr. E.R. Irwin, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 912)
  - Industrial Engineering, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 913)
  - Invitations: Inauguration, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 914)
  - Invitations: Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 915)
  - Invitations: Miscellaneous B, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 916)
  - Invitations- C, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 917)
  - J-miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 918)
  - Johnston, J. Ambler, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 919)
  - K-miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 920)
  - L-miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 921)
  - The Lane Company Inc.: Board of Visitors, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 922)
  - Legislation: General #1, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 923)
  - Legislation: General #2, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 924)
  - Library: Mr. F.C. Shirk, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 925)
  - Mechanical Engineering: Dr. J. Benerley Jones, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 926)
  - M-miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 927)
  - Metals & Ceramics Engineering: Dr. J.F. Eckel, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 928)
  - Military, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 929)
  - Mining Engineering: Dr. J. Richard Lucas, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 930)
  - Miscellaneous-General, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 931)
  - McCormick Farm, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 932)
  - N-miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 933)
  - NASA, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 934)
  - Name Change, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 935)
  - Naming Buildings, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 936)
  - National Research Council, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 937)
  - National Science Foundation, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 938)
  - National Education Association (NEA), 1967 (Box 25, Folder 939)
  - O-miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 940)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 941)
  - Organization, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 942)
  - P-miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 943)
  - Personnel: Albin T. Butt, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 944)
  - Personnel: Richmond- Mr. J.W. Garber, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 945)
  - Physical Education: Dr. W.E. McCubbin, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 946)
  - Physics: Dr. J.A. Jacobs, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 947)
  - Physical Planning: Mr. H.P.C. Vandenberg, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 948)
  - Philippines: Dr. Hahn Trip, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 949)
  - Placement: Dr. W.H. Cato, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 950)
  - Planning: Division of Governor's Office, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 951)
  - Plant Pathology and Physiology: Dr. H.B. Couch, Jr., 1967 (Box 26, Folder 952)
  - Department of Political Science, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 953)
  - Poly-Scientific, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 954)
  - Poultry Science: Dr. C.E. Howes, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 955)
  - President's Reports, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 956)
  - Psychology and Sociology Department, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 957)
  - Purchasing: Mr. James L. Schatts, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 958)
  - Q-miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 959)
  - R-miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 960)
  - Registrar, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 961)
  - Regional Educational Laboratory, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 962)
  - Research Corporation, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 963)
  - Research Division: Dean W.B. Harrison, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 964)
  - Reston "A", 1967 (Box 26, Folder 965)
  - Reston "B", 1967 (Box 26, Folder 966)
  - Retirement: Faculty, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 967)
  - Roanoke Electrical Steel, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 968)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 969)
  - Savage, Mr. Lon K., 1967 (Box 26, Folder 970)
  - S-miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 971)
  - Scholarships: Harry F. Byrd, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 972)
  - Scholarships and Grants #1, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 973)
  - Scholarships and Grants #2, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 974)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 975)
  - Speaking Engagements: Correspondence 1, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 976)
  - Speaking Engagements: Correspondence 2, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 977)
  - Speech Material, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 978)
  - State Board of Education, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 979)
  - Smithfield, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 980)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 981)
  - Statistics, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 982)
  - Staff, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 983)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 984)
  - Student Letters: To and From, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 985)
  - Student Letters: Others, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 986)
  - Student Organizations, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 987)
  - Student Affairs: Dean of Women- Dean Martha Harder, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 988)
  - Student Affairs: Dean of Men- J. Gordon Brown, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 989)
  - Student Affairs: Dean of Students- Dr. J.W. Dean 1, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 990)
  - Student Affairs: Dean of Students- Dr. J.W. Dean 2, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 991)
  - Student Affairs: Dean Al Payne, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 992)
  - Student Union, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 993)
  - Summer Conference, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 994)
  - T-miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 995)
  - Tech Festival, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 996)
  - TIAA, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 997)
  - TRW, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 998)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 999)
  - University Council #1, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1000)
  - University Council #2, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1001)
  - University Research Park, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1002)
  - University Services and Auxiliary Enterprises, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1003)
  - U-miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1004)
  - VPI Educational Foundation, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1005)
  - Veterinary Science, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1006)
  - Va. State Chamber of Commerce, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1007)
  - Vice President for Academic: Dr. W.W. Brandt, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1008)
  - Vice President for Administration: Presidents' Funds, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1009)
  - Vice President for Administration: Mr. S.K. Cassell, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1010)
  - Virginia Agricultural Conference Board, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1011)
  - Virginia Department of Agriculture, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1012)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1013)
  - Virginia Tech Student Aid, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1014)
  - Virginia Truck Experiment Station, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1015)
  - Virginia Tech Athletic Association, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1016)
  - Visiting Scholar Program, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1017)
  - W-miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1018)
  - Water Resources, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1019)
  - Wesley Foundation, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1020)
  - Wine Awards, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1021)
  - Y-miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1022)
  - YMCA, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1023)
  - A-miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1024)
  - Accountant: Mr. Carl E. Burke, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1025)
  - Accrediting- National Commission of Accrediting-ECPB, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1026)
  - Admission and Records: Dr. M.P. Lacy, Dean, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1027)
  - Aerospace Engineering: Dr. R.F. DeJarnette, Acting Head, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1028)
  - College of Agriculture: Dean James E. Martin, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1029)
  - Agricultural College: Dr. Wilson B. Bell, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1030)
  - Agriculture: Resident Instruction- Dr. T.J. Harne, Director, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1031)
  - Agricultural Engineering: Prof. U.F. Earp, Acting Head, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1032)
  - Agriculture and Life Science Research Division: Dr. Coyt Wilson, Director, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1032a)
  - Agronomy: Dr. T.B. Hutcheson, Head, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1033)
  - Aircraft, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1034)
  - Airport, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1035)
  - Air University, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1036)
  - Alumni President, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1037)
  - Alumni Contributions, Alphabetical, 28-1038 (Box 28, Folder 1038)
  - Alumni Association- General, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1039)
  - Alumni-Alphabetical, A-J, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1040)
  - Alumni- Alphabetical, K-Z, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1041)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1042)
  - American Association for Higher Education, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1043)
  - American Association for University Women, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1044)
  - American Council on Education, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1045)
  - Animal Sciences, Professor G.W. Lytton, Head, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1046)
  - Animal Industry Day, July 26, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1047)
  - Applications-Positions, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1048)
  - Architecture, College of: Dean Charles Burchard, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1049)
  - Arts and Sciences, College of: Dean Leslie F. Malpass, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1050)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1051)
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities (Southern), 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1052)
  - Association of Land Grant colleges and State Universities (National), 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1053)
  - Association of State Colleges and Universities, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1054)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1055)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1056)
  - Attorney General of Virginia, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1057)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises and University Services, Mr. H.W. Swink, Director, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1058)
  - B-miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1059)
  - Bailey Research Trust, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1060)
  - Basketball, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1061)
  - Bequests, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1062)
  - Biochemistry and Nutrition: Dr. Kendall W. King, Head, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1063)
  - Biographics, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1064)
  - Biology: Dr. R.A. Peterson, Head, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1065)
  - Blacksburg, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1066)
  - Bond Issue, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1067)
  - Budget Director: Mr. L.M. Kuhn, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1068)
  - Budget Matters #1, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1069)
  - Budget Matters #2, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1070)
  - Buildings and Grounds: Mr. W.M. Sterritt, Director, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1071)
  - Business, College of: Dean H.H. Mitchell, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1072)
  - Business Manager: Mr. E.B. Evans, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1073)